Guide to the Al Qassim Family Collection of photographs AD.MC.031
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Al Qassim Family Collection Prints (Object AD_MC_031_ref168)
  - View of houses in Bur Dubai. 6.2 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref90)
    Landscapes; Architecture; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Houses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings
  - Landscape of Dubai. 6.8 x 8.8, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref91)
    Water; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Buildings; Landscapes; Architecture; Buildings
  - Landscape view of Bur Dubai. 6.9 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref92)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Buildings; Architecture; Buildings
  - View of Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref93)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Water; Buildings; Houses
  - View of Khor Dubai from above. 6.3 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref94)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Boats/Ships; Landscapes; Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Water
  - Landscape of Bur Dubai. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref95)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Boats/Ships; Water; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Buildings; Houses; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing
  - Landscape view of Khor Dubai. 6.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref96)
    Landscapes; Architecture; Construction; Water; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Boats/Ships; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Ports; Arabic Writing; Houses; Buildings
  - View of Khor Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref97)
    Water; Buildings; Houses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Houses at the edge of Khor Dubai. 6.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref98)
    Boats/Ships; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Boats/Ships; Landscapes; Architecture; Houses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Buildings
  - Umm Al-Quwain from a far. 6.7 x 9.0 cm, 25 February 1965 (Object AD_MC_031_ref99)
    Landscapes; Buildings; Water; Umm Al-Quwain, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Landscape of mountains in Masafi, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.8 x 8.8 cm, 25 February 1965 (Object AD_MC_031_ref100)
    Outdoors; Palm Trees; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Animals; Agriculture/Farms; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes
  - Desert in Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref101)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Deserts; Landscapes; Countryside/Rural; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
  - Landscape of the desert in Al-Dhaid. 6.3 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref102)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; Countryside/Rural; Outdoors; Landscapes; Outdoors; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Outdoors; Photographic Prints
  - Al-Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.4 x 8.7, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref103)
    Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Countryside/Rural; Landscapes; Deserts; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Landscape of Al-Salehia. 6.4 x 6.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref104)
    Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Landscapes
  - View of Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref105)
    Outdoors; Agriculture/Farms; Arabic Writing; Landscapes; Houses; Outdoors; Palm Trees; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Architecture
  - Mushrif Area, Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref106)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; Landscapes; Outdoors
  - Al-Dhaid desert, Sharjah. 6.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref107)
    Deserts; Outdoors; Deserts; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Outdoors; Landscapes
  - Farm in Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref108)
    Outdoors; Agriculture/Farms; Palm Trees; Palm Trees; Outdoors; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes
  - Landscape of Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref109)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Agriculture/Farms; Deserts; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Landscapes
  - Shinas, Oman. 6.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref110)
    Oman; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Mountains/Hills; Deserts; Landscapes
  - Landscape of Al Kharran desert in Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref111)
    Outdoors; Deserts; Outdoors; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Man in front of the sea with Umm Al-Quwain in the background. 6.8 x 9.0 cm, 25 February 1965 (Object AD_MC_031_ref112)
    Landscapes; Men; Water; Arabian/Persian Gulf; Beaches; Umm Al-Quwain, United Arab Emirates; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Al-Salehia desert, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref113)
    Countryside/Rural; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Outdoors; Landscapes; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Deserts
  - Desert in Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref114)
    Landscapes; Countryside/Rural; Outdoors; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Deserts; Arabic Writing; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A goat in an old house in Deira, Dubai. 6.6 x 8.7 cm, Circa 1960-1969 (Object AD_MC_031_ref115)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Houses; Animals; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Goats
  - Official portrait of Sabah Salem Al Mubarak Al Sabah Emir of Kuwait. 8.8 x 6.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref116)
    Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Officials
  - Portrait of Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum. 8.8 x 6.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref117)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Officials; Men; Royalty; Political Leadership; Facial Hair; Signs/Signposts; Officials; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - Men and boys walking during Sheikh Rashid's reception at the Dubai airport. 4.9 x 7.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref118)
    Sheikhs; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Airports; Boys; Men; Children; Group Portraits; Royalty; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - Group of men waiting during Sheikh Rashid's reception at the Dubai Airport. 5.2 x 7.3 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref119)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheikhs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Airports; Regional/National Dress; Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Royalty; Political Leadership; Officials; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - View of Khor Dubai from above. 6.7 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref120)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Water; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Architecture; Houses
  - Al Kharran, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.7 cm, 8 March 1962 (Object AD_MC_031_ref121)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Animals; Deserts; Outdoors; Outdoors; Landscapes; Arabic Writing; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Photographic Prints
  - Group of men in the Al Kharran desert. 6.6 x 8.6 cm, 8 March 1962 (Object AD_MC_031_ref122)
    Outdoors; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Countryside/Rural; Outdoors; Deserts; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Landscapes
  - Group of men welcoming Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum at the Dubai Airport. 5.0 x 7.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref123)
    Sheikhs; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airports; Regional/National Dress; Men; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Group Portraits; Royalty; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - Men greeting Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum at the Dubai Airport. 5.3 x 7.4 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref124)
    Regional/National Dress; Crowds; Sheikhs; Airports; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Royalty; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - Boys swimming in Khatt Spring, Ras Al Khaimah. 6.0 x 5.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref125)
    Palm Trees; Outdoors; Springs; Water; Men; Boys; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Group Portraits
  - Farm in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref126)
    Outdoors; Palm Trees; Agriculture/Farms; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Landscapes
  - A man shaking hands with Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum at the Dubai Airport. 5.1 x 7.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref127)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Crowds; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Airports; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Men; Group Portraits; Royalty; Political Leadership; Officials; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - A group of men at the Dubai Aiport for Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception. 5.3 x 7.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref128)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Regional/National Dress; Cars/Trucks; Airplanes; Airports; Transportation; Group Portraits; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - A group of men disembarking an Iran Air plane at the Dubai Airport. 5.1 x 7.3, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref129)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikhs; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Iran; Airplanes; Airports; Group Portraits; Royalty; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - A group of men at the Dubai Aiport during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's Reception. 5.3 x 7.3 cm, 1965 (Object AD_MC_031_ref130)
    Sheikhs; Crowds; Regional/National Dress; Airports; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Royalty; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - A man holding a child at the Dubai Airport during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception. 5.1 x 7.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref131)
    Boys; Children; Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheikhs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Airports; Group Portraits; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - Date palm trees in Filli, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref132)
    Countryside/Rural; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Palm Trees
  - Two men in Khatt, Ras Al Khaimah. 8.7 x 6.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref133)
    Agriculture/Farms; Cameras; Men; Water; Irrigation; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Palm Trees; Group Portraits
  - Boys by the irrigation system in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref134)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Water; Agriculture/Farms; Irrigation; Boys; Outdoors; Children; Group Portraits
  - Desert of Al Kharran, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref135)
    Deserts; Outdoors; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Countryside/Rural; Landscapes
  - Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref136)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Landscapes
  - Landscape of Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref137)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Countryside/Rural; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors
  - Men working on a construction in Al-Dhaid. 6.4 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref138)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Construction; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits
  - Boy posing behind tobacco plants in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 8.7 x 6.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref139)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Agriculture/Farms; Deserts; Outdoors; Boys; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
  - Two men next to a truck in Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref140)
    Cars/Trucks; Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Group Portraits
  - View from a mosque in Khor Dubai. 6.4 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref141)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Boats/Ships; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Water
  - Landscape of Dubai from above. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref142)
    Buildings; Houses; Palm Trees; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Landscapes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Landscape of Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref143)
    Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Countryside/Rural; Deserts
  - View of houses in Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref144)
    Architecture; Buildings; Houses; Landscapes; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Water
  - View of Dubai from Bur Dubai. 6.3 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref145)
    Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Landscapes
  - View of the Arabian Gulf, Dubai. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, 25 August 1964 (Object AD_MC_031_ref146)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Boats/Ships; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabian/Persian Gulf; Water; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
  - Men inside tent in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref147)
    Deserts; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Tents; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Mountains in Masafi, Dubai. 6.8 x 8.9 cm, 25 February 1965 (Object AD_MC_031_ref148)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Palm Trees; Mountains/Hills; Arabic Writing; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Landscapes
  - Group of men on a trip in Al Kharran, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref149)
    Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Men; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Tents; Group Portraits
  - Crowd surrounding a car during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception at the Dubai Airport. 6.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref150)
    Crowds; Airports; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Cars/Trucks; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Transportation; Group Portraits; Royalty; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - Two boys in front of a tent in Al Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref151)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Tents; Men; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress
  - Landscape of Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref152)
    Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Palm Trees; Houses; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Deserts; Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Buildings
  - A car in front of a crowd of men during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception at the Dubai Airport. 8.8 x 6.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref153)
    Sheikhs; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cars/Trucks; Regional/National Dress; Airports; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Transportation; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - A minaret of a mosque in Dubai. 6.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref154)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Mosques; Architecture; Religious Sites
  - A water tank in Dubai. 6.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref155)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Water
  - View of stores in Deira, Dubai. 6.3 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref156)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Shops; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Men swimming in the hot springs in Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref157)
    Swimming; Springs; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Men; Water; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - Landscape of the coast of Oman. 8.8 x 6.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref158)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Seas; Oman; Coast; Beaches; Landscapes
  - Man inside tower of Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 8.6 x 6.7 cm, 25 August 1964 (Object AD_MC_031_ref159)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Individual Portraits
  - A crowd of people during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception at the Dubai Airport. 6.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref160)
    Sheikhs; Airports; Audiences/Spectators; Regional/National Dress; Men; Crowds; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Police; Boys; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Children; Group Portraits; Royalty; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - View of the sea on the road between Dubai and Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.7, Undated (Object AD_MC_031_ref161)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Water; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Beaches; Seas
- Al Qassim Family Slides